myhealthtips.in 2018-03-01

# Privacy Policy - My Health Tips - My Health Tips

At MyHealthTips.in we recognize that privacy of your personal information is very important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our site MyHealthTips.in  and how we safeguard your information. The basic rules we follow are as follows:

  * We don’t ask for your personal information unless we truly need it
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site

**Our policy is to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.**  
**  
**

### Log Files

Like most website operators, MyHealthTips.in collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MyHealthTips.in’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MyHealthTips.in’s visitors use its website. From time to time, MyHealthTips.in may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

MyHealthTips.in also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. MyHealthTips.in only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to MyHealthTips.in’s websites choose to interact with MyHealthTips.in in ways that require MyHealthTips.in to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that MyHealthTips.in gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive MyHealthTips.in updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, MyHealthTips.in collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with MyHealthTips.in. MyHealthTips.in does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

MyHealthTips.in may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, MyHealthTips.in may monitor the most popular pages on the MyHealthTips.in site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. MyHealthTips.in may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, MyHealthTips.int does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
MyHealthTips.in discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that: (i) need to know that information in order to process it on MyHealthTips.in’s behalf or to provide services available at MyHealthTips.in’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using MyHealthTips.in’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MyHealthTips.in will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above,MyHealthTips.in discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when MyHealthTips.in believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MyHealthTips.in, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an MyHealthTips.in website and have supplied your email address, MyHealthTips.in may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with MyHealthTips.in and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. MyHealthTips.in takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Third Party Advertisement

We may also use third party advertisements on MyHealthTips.in to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MyHealthTips.in and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does “NOT” track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, MyHealthTips.in may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MyHealthTips.in’s sole discretion. MyHealthTips.in encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you have any questions regarding the policy, you may contact MyHealthTips.in’s staff by using our contact form.
